tweetmysong.com 2013-08-05

# TweetMySong Privacy Policy

TweetMySong is committed to protecting your privacy online. We are also committed to providing you with the very best experience we can on our Web site. In order to enhance your experience at our site we gather certain personal information about you that helps us customize our content to your tastes and preferences. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of our Web site. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.

### What information do we collect? 

TweetMySong collects information in several ways from different parts of our Web site.

TweetMySong collects some personal information when you initially sign in to our free services. We collect your name, location, and other Twitter™ information.

Wherever TweetMySong collects personal information, we make an effort to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.

### What information do parties other than TweetMySong collect?

Some advertisers or Web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you when you access or utilize those links. TweetMySong does not control the collection or use of such information, and the practices of those advertisers and Web sites are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

Some advertisers or Web sites that have links on our site may also use their own cookies.

If you do not wish to allow for use of cookies, you can generally opt-out of providing this information by setting your browser to reject cookies. However, please be aware that some areas may not provide you with an acceptable user experience if you have disabled the use of cookies.

### What do we do with the information we collect? 

TweetMySong's primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience on our Web site. The information we collect (including information contained in your cookie) may be used to provide such capabilities as personalization services and personalized communication between you and the artists you prefer. We may also use the information to estimate the size of our audience and measure certain traffic patterns, to track the progress and number of entries in our promotions and contests, to notify our visitors about updates to our Web site, to contact you for marketing purposes. 

In addition, if we feel that a user abuses the TweetMySong site in any way, we reserve the right to share certain information with third parties. Abuses include (but are not limited to) possible copyright infringement, possible libel and slander.

### With whom do we share your information and for what purpose? 

TweetMySong does not sell, rent, or trade your personal information with others. However, when one or more of our business partners co-sponsor a service, promotion and/or contest, we may share some or all of the information collected in connection with such service, promotion or contest with the co-sponsor(s). If you do not want your information to be shared, you will be able to choose not to allow the transfer by not using or signing up for that particular service, promotion or contest.

### Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on TweetMySong. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  

### Your Consent 

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by Tweet My Song as outlined in this Privacy Policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy 

From time to time, we may change our Privacy Policy. We will post those changes on this page so that our customers will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we share the information with others.
